And that's why
no matter what Mommy says
we really were on a break.
Yes, we were.
Come here, gorgeous.
Oh, look at you.
You are the cutest
little baby ever.
You're just a little-bitty baby,
you know that?
But you've got...
you've got big, beautiful eyes.
Yes, you do.
And a big, round belly.
A big, baby butt.
I like big butts.
♪ I like big butts
and I cannot lie ♪
♪ You other brothers
can't deny ♪
♪ When a girl walks in
with an itty-bitty waist ♪
♪ And a round thing
in your face, you get... ♪
Oh, my God, Emma.
You're laughing.
Oh, my God, you've never
done that before, have you?
You've never done that before.
Daddy made you laugh, huh?
Well, Daddy and Sir Mix-A-Lot.
What? What?
You want to hear some more?
♪ My anaconda don't want none ♪
♪ Unless you got buns, hon... ♪
I'm a terrible father.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey.
Listen, what do you guys
know about investments?
How come?
I'm starting to make good money
on the show
and I'm thinking I should
probably do something with it.
What do you do
with your money now?
It's taped to the back
of my toilet tank.
I didn't say that.
It's in a bank,
guarded by robots.
Do you have any ideas?
Yeah, this guy at work
got me excited
about going in
on an emu farm.
That'd be
kind of cool, huh?
Pitching in on the weekends,
helping to plant the emus.
Joe, emus are birds.
You raise them for meat.
( laughs ):
Yuh, right.
People eat birds.
Bird meat.
Now do they just fly
into your mouth?
Or do you go into
a restaurant and say
"Excuse me, I'll have
a bucket of fried bird"?
Or "maybe just a wing or a..."
Joey, I think
you should consider
something a little less risky.
I think in this market
real estate is
your best investment.
The Fed just
lowered the rates
and the interest
on your mortgage
is totally deductible.
That's right,
I know some stuff.
Real estate, huh?
Oh, and you know who's selling
a great apartment? Richard.
And you know whose knowledge
of her ex-boyfriend is shocking?
Monica.
My dad told me.
They play golf together.
Oh, well, maybe
I'll join them sometime.
I just hope the club
doesn't slip out of my hand
and beat the mustache
off his face.
Hi.
Listen, you have
to help me pick a dress
'cause I'm meeting
Mike's parents tonight.
Wow, the
boyfriend's parents.
That's a big step.
Really?
That hadn't occurred to me.
Sweetie, they're going
to love you-- just be yourself.
They live on the Upper East Side
on Park Avenue.
Oh, yeah, she can't be herself.
Okay, so...
all right, which dress?
You can say neither.
Neither.
Oh, God, neither.
I'm sorry, honey.
We'll take you shopping.
It's going to be fine.
Yeah, totally.
You are in such good hands.
And I am so good
with meeting parents.
With the father, you know,
you want to flirt a little bit
but not in a gross way.
Just kind of like,
"Oh, Mr. Pinzer
I can see where Wallace
gets his good looks."
You went out
with Wallace Pinzer?
Oh, he took
the SATs for me.
I knew you didn't get a 1,400.
Well, duh!
So, now,
what about with Mike's mom?
Oh, well, with the mother
just constantly tell her
how amazing her son is.
Take it from me.
Moms love me.
Ross's mom one time
actually said
I am like the daughter
that she never had.
She said what?
That she's like the daughter
she never had.
Listen.
Hi.
I just finished getting Phoebe
all dressed
to meet Mike's parents.
She's so nervous.
It's so sweet.
Guess what.
I made Emma laugh today.
You what?!
And I missed it?
Because I was
giving a makeover
to that stupid hippie?!
Yeah, and it was...
it was like
a real little person
laugh, too.
It was like, um...
( screechy giggling )
Only... only not creepy.
What did you do
to make her laugh?
I, um... well, I sang.
Actually, I rapped...
um... "Baby Got Back."
You what?
You sang to our baby daughter
a song about a guy
who likes to have sex
with women with giant asses?!
But you know what?
If you think about it
it actually promotes
a healthy body image.
Because even big butts
or "juicy doubles" are...
( groans )
Please don't take her
away from me.
Oh, hi. Come on in.
I'm Catherine,
the listing agent.
Hi, I'm Joey,
this is Chandler.
So, how come Richard's
selling the place?
Went bankrupt?
Medical malpractice?
Choked on his own mustache?
Actually, he's buying
a much bigger place.
It's got a great view
of Central Park...
Ah, that's enough
out of you.
Is there anything we should know
about the apartment?
All of the appliances
are included.
There's a lot of light,
a new kitchen.
I think you guys
would be very happy here.
( chuckling )
Oh, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
No!
No, no,
we're not together.
We're not a couple.
We're definitely not
a couple.
Oh, okay, sorry.
Wow, you seemed pretty insulted
by that.
What, I'm not
good enough for you?
We are not going to have
this conversation again.
Look at this place.
Why am I so intimidated
by this guy?
Pretentious art...
this huge, macho couch.
When we know all he does
is sit around all day
crying about losing Monica
to a real man.
You don't think
he's here, do you?
You know, it's a nice place.
But I got to say, I don't know
if I see myself living here.
Well, let me see.
Yeah, I can see it.
Look at these videos.
I mean, who does he think he is?
Magnum Force, Dirty Harry,
Cool Hand Luke...
Oh, my God.
What?
There's a tape here
with Monica's name on it.
Ooh, a tape with
a girl's name on it.
It's probably a sex tape.
Wait a minute.
This says "Monica."
And this is Richard's apartment.
Get there faster!
( gasps )
Wow.
You look...
like my mom.
I'm wearing pantyhose.
Great.
Come on in.
Hi.
Thank you.
Oh.
Oh, my God, you're rich.
No, my parents
are rich.
So? They got to die
someday.
Hello.
Mom, Dad,
this is Phoebe.
Phoebe, these
are my parents,
Theodore and Bitsy.
( affected manner ):
Theodore, Bitsy.
What a delight.
It's so nice
to finally meet you.
And you.
Your home is lovely.
Thank you.
I'll give you a tour later.
It's actually three floors.
( still affected ):
Holy crap.
Phoebe, why don't you
come in the living room
and meet our friends?
Try and stop me.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm trying to get
your parents to like me.
Yeah, I'm sure they will.
But you don't
have to do this.
I want them to get
to know Phoebe, not...
( affected ):
Phoebe.
( still affected ):
You got it.
It's hard to stop.
Well, come on.
Phoebe, these are
our friends
Tom and Sue Engel.
Phoebe, come sit.
Tell us a little bit
about yourself.
So where are you from?
Um... okay.
( normal voice ):
Well, all right, um...
Originally I'm from upstate.
But then my mom
killed herself
and my step-dad
went to prison.
So I just...
moved to the city
where I actually lived
in a burned out Buick
LeSabre for a while.
Which was okay,
that was okay
until I got hepatitis
you know, 'cause...
this pimp spit in
my mouth, and...
But I got over it.
And, um... anyway,
now I'm a freelance
massage therapist
which, you know, isn't
always steady money
but at least I don't
pay taxes, you know?
( affected manner ):
So where does
everyone summer?
Oh, God, this is
not going well.
No, no, you're
doing fine, really.
Why don't you go
talk to my dad.
Okay, okay, okay.
Still sure about
me being myself?
Absolutely.
Maybe just...
a little less pimp spit.
Okay.
So, Theodore...
I can see where Mike
gets his good looks from.
Oh, well...
And that physique.
You must work out
all the time.
No, not all the time.
I do the best I can.
Yeah, I bet.
Look out.
Oh, ow!
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
( groaning ):
I... recently
had surgery.
I'm so sorry.
No, I'll be fine.
I just... should
check the stitches.
I really, really
am sorry.
How could you know?
Why wouldn't you
punch me in the stomach?
Um, did you just
hit my dad?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I've never met
a boyfriend's
parents before.
But you have met
humans before, right?
Look, why don't you go
talk to my mom.
Yeah, okay, yeah,
your mom, okay.
She looks nice.
I can talk to her.
You do that
and then I'm going
to go check my dad for signs
of internal bleeding.
Yeah. Okay.
Oh, Bitsy, hi.
Listen, I just wanted
to thank you again
for having me
here tonight.
Well, not at all.
Also I just want you to
know what a wonderful
man your son is.
Thank you.
I think so, too.
Well, and it really
is a testament to
how he was raised.
Especially to you
because he's very
respectful of women.
Is he really?
Are you kidding?
He is so considerate
of my feelings
and, you know, I think
you'd also like to know
that he is
a very gentle lover.
Excuse me?
Oh, no, no,
no, no.
Don't get me wrong.
No, not in like
a sissy way.
No, no, no.
When he gets going,
he can rattle a headboard
like a sailor on leave.
That's... my boy.
Awesome.
I'm not going to watch it.
I don't need to watch it.
I mean, what good could possibly
come from watching it?
Well, we know I'm going
to watch it.
Hey, dude, what's up?
Don't judge me. I'm only human!
Did you take that tape?
I had to. Okay, imagine
you were married
and you found a tape
of your wife in another
guy's apartment.
Wouldn't you need
to know to know
what was on it?
I don't know.
Who am I married to?
Some girl.
She hot?
Yeah.
How did she get me
to settle down?
All right, I'm
going to watch it.
I mean, look, it's
probably not even
what I think it is.
And even if it is,
it can't possibly
be as bad
as what I'm picturing
in my head.
Can it?
I don't know.
In my experience,
if a girl says yes
to being taped
she doesn't say no to much else,
I'll tell you.
Then you're going to have
to watch it for me.
What? Whoa. What?
Just for a few seconds
so I can know what
it is. Please?
All right, fine.
But if I enjoy this
you have only
yourself to blame.
( crowd cheering )
Why am I hearing
cheering?
Well, it's okay.
It's just a football game.
Football? It's just football?
Yeah. See? You were
all worried for nothing.
It's football!
It's just football!
This is great.
This is the first time
I've ever enjoyed football.
I think it may be customary
to get a beer.
( erotic moaning )
What the...?
What are you doing?!
You don't want to see
what I just saw!
What are you guys doing?
Oh, my God!
Is that Richard?!
Okay.
Please laugh for Mommy.
Please.
Please laugh
for Mommy.
( blowing raspberry )
Not funny, huh?
Well, so is it... only offensive
novelty rap?
Or maybe just. you know,
rap in general?
'Cause Mommy can rap.
♪ My name is Mommy ♪
♪ And I'm here to say ♪
♪ That all the babies... ♪
Oh, I can't rap.
All right, sweetheart.
This is only because
I love you so much
and I know that you're not
going to tell anybody.
♪ I like... big butts
and I cannot lie ♪
♪ You other brothers
can't deny ♪
♪ When a girl walks in
with an itty-bitty waist ♪
♪ And a round thing
in your face... ♪
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes!
♪ I like big butts ♪
♪ And I cannot lie ♪
♪ You other brothers
can't deny... ♪
Oh, Emma, you're laughing.
Oh, you are.
You really do like
big butts, don't you?
Oh, you beautiful
little weirdo.
Hey.
You missed it.
She was laughing.
Oh, it was amazing.
It was amazing.
It was the most beautiful,
beautiful sound.
Oh, I know. Isn't it?
What'd you do to get
her to laugh?
Uh... you know, I just...
a couple of things,
I tried... different thing.
"Itsy Bitsy Spider."
You sang "Baby Got Back,"
didn't you?
Nothing else works.
That girl is all about
the ass.
And then it goes
back to the chorus--
♪ Smelly cat,
smelly cat ♪
♪ It's not your fault. ♪
And that's the end
of the song.
I realize you hadn't asked
to hear it, but, um...
no one had spoken
in 17 minutes.
So, Phoebe writes
lots of great songs.
What was that one you sang
the other night
that everybody just loved?
Oh, "Pervert Parade"?
No...
Oh, "Ode to a Pubic Hair"?
Stop.
Oh, God.
Is that veal?
Mom, I thought I told you,
Phoebe's a vegetarian.
Oh...
Oh, no, no, that's okay.
That's okay.
I mean, I am a vegetarian,
except for veal.
Yeah... no, veal I love.
Phoebe, you don't
have to eat that.
Actually, it's any baby animals.
Kittens, fish babies.
But, you know, especially veal.
And this... this nice vein
of fat running through it.
Mm, yummy.
So...
what do you think?
So you stole that tape
from Richard's apartment?
Oh, listen to the judgment
from the porn star.
That tape was never meant
to be seen by...
Joey, I would feel
more comfortable
if I was having this
conversation in private.
Monica, look, I don't think you
and I have any secrets anymore.
Not ready to joke
about it yet.
Okay, I'll see you later.
Why in the world
would you take this tape?
And why would you watch it?
Because that's who I am, okay?
I'm sure
a mature man like Richard
could see a tape like that
and it wouldn't bother him.
Just be another saucy anecdote
for him to share
at his men's club
over brandy
and mustaches.
Is all of this about
you not being able
to grow a mustache?
This is about
you and Richard.
He's clearly
not over you.
He keeps a tape
so he can look at it
whenever he wants.
Isn't that sad?
I mean, can you see
how pathetic that is?
You shouldn't be jealous.
You should feel bad for him.
Oh, yeah, well, poor Richard.
I can grow a mustache.
Chandler, this is
not our problem.
We've got each other.
That's all that matters.
Yeah, but I just keep
picturing you
rolling around with him
with your cowboy boots
in the air.
Cowboy boots?
I've never worn
cowboy boots in
my whole life.
Good, good, play more.
'Cause I want to see
how it ends.
That's not me.
What?
That's not you!
Life is good again.
Ride 'em, cowgirl!
That bastard
taped over me.
Is that a problem?
Well, it's just
so insulting.
I mean, spring
for a new blank
tape, Doctor.
I can't imagine what
he sees in her.
She actually makes me miss
that pill-popping
ex-wife of his.
Oh, hello, dear.
Hey.
What's going on?
We were just chitchatting.
How's your friend?
A little better.
By the way, do you know
who's moving back into town?
Tom and Sue's
daughter Jen.
You remember
her, Michael.
She's lovely and well-behaved
and single.
I'm not interested.
Oh, please, darling,
let's be honest.
You can have all the sailor fun
you want with that one
but let's be real.
All right, stop.
You know, all Phoebe
has done tonight
is try and get you
to like her.
Maybe that hasn't
been clear all the time
but she did her best.
And yeah, she's a little
different than you are.
Michael, a pimp
spit in her mouth.
MIKE:
So what?
I mean, if I
can get past that
it shouldn't
bother you.
And you don't have
to like her.
You just have to accept
the fact that I do.
I mean, if you can't even
be civil to the woman I love...
The woman you what?
Yeah, the woman
you what?
The woman I love.
I love you.
Which is probably something
I shouldn't say
for the first time in
front of my parents...
and Tom and Sue...
who are, by the way, the most
sinfully boring people
I've ever met in my life.
I love you, too.
You do?
Yeah.
How great is this?
Want to get out of here?
Okay.
Mom, Dad,
thanks for dinner.
I had a great time.
( affected ):
It was really
top drawer.
And here's something rich--
13 bathrooms in this place--
I threw up in the coat closet.
Ta-ta.
♪ So, fellas ♪
♪ Yeah? ♪
♪ Fellas ♪
♪ Has your girlfriend
got the butt? ♪
♪ Hell, yeah ♪
♪ So shake it ♪
♪ Shake it ♪
♪ Shake that nasty butt ♪
♪ Baby got back ♪
♪ One more time
from the top ♪
♪ I like big butts
and I cannot lie... ♪
♪ You other broth... ♪
Rachel, please, that
is so inappropriate.